Guide to the Planned Community Archives collection, 1960-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Reston, 1961-2006
  - Subseries 8: Scrapbook, 1961-1980
    - DC Suburbs and Plans to Show Town Houses, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 102)
      498C.27
    - First Reston Homes Open, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 103)
      498C.28
    - Reston is Opening its First Doors, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 104)
      498C.29
    - Reston's First Model Town, 1960s (Box 26, Folder 105)
      498C.30
    - Reston's First Village Features Cluster Housing Near Lake Anne, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 106)
      498C.31
    - New Community Offers Piped Air Conditioning, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 107)
      498C.32
    - One Good Turn..., 1964 (Box 26, Folder 108)
      498C.33
    - Echoes-A Great Dream, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 109)
      498C.34
    - Reston's Lake Anne village Opening to Public, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 110)
      498C.35
    - Reston Town Houses To Open Sunday, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 111)
      498C.36
    - A Likely Source for Revenue Bond, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      498C.37
    - Central Plant Will Air Cool Entire Town, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      498C.38
    - Reston's Repute is Worldwide, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      498C.39
    - Village Sets Central Heat, Cooling Unit, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      498C.40
    - Reston Development Takes a City Look, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      498C.41
    - Sauce for the Gander New Towns, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      498C.42
    - Golf Course, Rail Transit, Dulles Light, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      498C.43
    - Virginia Called Derelict in Gaining US Offices, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      498C.44
    - Reston, Virginia, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      498C.45
    - Reston Creator HOnored, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      498C.46
    - Railroad is Praised for Suburb Service, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      498D.01
    - Japanese Beat the Heat by Utilizing Psychology, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 12)
      498D.03
    - Washington Galleries Tour Progress at Reston, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      498D.04
    - James B. Selonick, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      498D.05
    - Progress: Some Examples, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      498D.06
    - Budget Analysis, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      498D.07
    - Modern Communities Planned to Provide Complete FAcilities, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      498D.08
    - Robert E. Simon, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      498D.09
    - New Community Planning Concepts, Solving Unruly Growth Problems, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      498D.10
    - Cities Built All at Once, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 20)
      498D.11
    - Bleak Outlook for W and OD Survival, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      498D.12
    - P.R. League Told About New Housing, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      498D.13
    - TCI Engineers Will Build In Reston Center, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      498D.14
    - Challenge is to Build Cities, Architects Told, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      498D.15
    - Northern Virginia Holds Fast Place, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 25)
      498D.16
    - Transportation Consultants Incorporated Buys Five Acres, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      498D.017
    - Northern Virginia Continues Big Strides, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 27)
      498D.19
    - Community Concept Gaining, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      498D.20
    - Cool Man in House, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      498D.21
    - Gallery of Art Set Tour, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 30)
      498D.22
    - Tennis Anyone, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 31)
      498D.23
    - Church Leaders Developing Program Religion for Town Still in Plan Stage, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 32)
      498D.24
    - Complete Air-Conditioned City, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 33)
      498D.25
    - Articles about Simon Enterprises, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 34)
      498D.26
    - Awards and Competitions, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 35)
      498D.27
    - Coordination-JB Selonick, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 36)
      498D.28
    - Suburbs with a Difference Being Built, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 37)
      498D.29
    - Skip-a-Long, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 38)
      498E.01
    - Around the Hill, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 39)
      498E.02
    - Engineering in New Town, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 40)
      498E.03
    - Some Communities, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 41)
      498E.04
    - Planned Community-Metropolitan News, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 42)
      498E.05
    - Article, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 43)
      498E.06
    - Tomorrow's Suburbs, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 44)
      498E.07
    - Letter From America, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 45)
      498E.08
    - Events at Washington Gallery, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 46)
      498E.09
    - Laver Seeded No. 1 at Reston, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 47)
      498E.10
    - Golf At Reston Starts Today, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 48)
      498E.11
    - Broad Living Range, City Building, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 49)
      498E.12
    - Planning For Beauty, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 50)
      498E.13
    - Where Will Foxes Go?, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 51)
      498E.14
    - Pro-Tennis Tourney is Benefit, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 52)
      498E.15
    - The Week End That Was, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 53)
      498E.16
    - President's Conference on Natural Beauty (Photo), 1965 (Box 27, Folder 54)
      498E.17
    - Hope for Housing, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 55)
      498E.18
    - The State of Real Estate and Building, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 56)
      498E.19
    - Land Values, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 57)
      498E.20
    - High Rise Goes Up at Reston Simon Stress Use Open Space, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 58)
      498E.21
    - Condensation of Remarks by Herman E. Johnson, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 59)
      498E.22
    - Castle and Cookie, Incorporated, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 60)
      498E.23
    - Standard Fruit Interest, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 61)
      498E.24
    - New Town in Virginia Hunt County, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 62)
      498E.25
    - Art Patrons Get a Peek at Reston, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 63)
      498E.26
    - Robert E. Simon Envelope, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 64)
      498E.27
    - Users Continue Please To Save W and OD Line, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 65)
      498E.28
    - Reston Model Interior (Newspaper Photo), 1965 (Box 27, Folder 66)
      498E.29
    - Personal Side of Real Estate Board Living Range Offered at Reston, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 67)
      498E.30
    - State of Real Estate and Building, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 68)
      498E.31
    - William G. Simon, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 69)
      498E.32
    - Skip-a-Long, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 70)
      498E.33
    - More Places to Play, But More, Players, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 71)
      498E.34
    - Novel Concept In Living Discussed At Davison, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 72)
      498E.35
    - Across the Net, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 73)
      498E.36
    - Individual Rated No. 1 at Reston, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 74)
      498E.37
    - Pro-Tennis Tourney Set for Reston, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 75)
      498E.38
    - Who Will Rule?, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 76)
      498E.39
    - Pro-Tennis Tour Comes to Reston, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 77)
      498E.40
    - It Started Out as Fun, But Then-, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 78)
      498E.41
    - New Society, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 79)
      498E.42
    - Professional Tennis Tournament Set for Reston, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 80)
      498E.43
    - Reston Trees (Newspaper Photo), 1965 (Box 27, Folder 81)
      498E.44
    - Engineers Explain Two New Communities, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 82)
      498E.45
    - A/C Likely For Cities of the Future, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 83)
      498E.46
    - Art Gallery to Open in Fall at Reston, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 84)
    - Washington Galleryites, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 85)
      498E.47
    - Economics of Beauty Stress by Simon, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 86)
      498E.48
    - New Towns-Completely Planned, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 87)
      498E.49
    - Towns Challenge Suburban Sprawl, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 88)
      498E.50
    - New Suburbia, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 89)
      498E.51
    - Beautiful Nation Aim of Experts, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 90)
      498E.52
    - Caption Writings, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 91)
      498E.53
    - Appraisers and Bankers Tend to Ignore Interim Increase in Land Values, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 92)
      498E.54
    - ...Divided into Villages, Town Plan, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 93)
    - Selonick and Simon, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 94)
      498E.56
    - Architect Says Race Barriers Must Be Ended, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 95)
      498E.57
    - Two Genuine New Town, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 96)
      498E.59
    - Occupancy Nearly Ready at Reston, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      498F.01
    - First Village Rising at Reston, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      498F.02
    - The American Home, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 3)
      498F.03
    - Portfolio-Published Newsletter, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      498F.04
    - US Budget Fine Print May Accelerate Land Development Boom, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      498F.05
    - Fairfax Population to Top a Million, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      498F.06
    - Robert E. Simon-Message to Secretary of the Interior, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 7)
      498F.07
    - Brand New City for Maryland, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      498F.08
    - Reston's First Model Townhouse Soon Will Be Ready for Viewing, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 9)
      498F.09
    - A Guide to Reston, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      498F.10
    - The Reston Story, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      498F.11
    - Structure and Design, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      498F.12
    - New Towns: Shape of Utopia, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      498F.13
    - Fairfax County, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      498F.14
    - West Gate of London, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      498F.15
    - Town Plan Said to Aid Family Life, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      498F.16
    - Could This Be Our Town, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 17)
      498F.17
    - Copies of New Articles, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      498F.18
    - Chatter!, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      498F.19
    - Planned Community-Today, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      498F.20
    - Washington World, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      498F.21
    - Washington World, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      498F.22
    - "Reston, Virginia" Napkins, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Reston Plans to Show Town Houses, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      498F.23
    - Opening Its First Doors, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      498F.24
    - Arts in Virginia, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 26)
      498F.25
    - Reston Center for Industry and Government, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 27)
      498F.26
    - Prospects and Problems, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 28)
      498F.27
    - Mr. Brockett, President, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 29)
      498F.28
    - Oil Firm's Interest in Housing, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 30)
      498F.29
    - First Mortgage Taken by Gulf, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 31)
      498F.30
    - Gulf Oil Invests in City Financing, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 32)
      498F.31
    - Air conditioning Piped Into Virginia Homes, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 33)
      498F.32
    - Sales Manager Named at Reston, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 34)
      498F.33
    - Two Sofas Solve Decorating Problems, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 35)
      498F.34
    - "League Lines", 1965 (Box 28, Folder 36)
      498F.35
    - Reynolds Building at Four Locations, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 37)
      498F.36
    - The State of Real Estate and Building, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 38)
      498F.37
    - Labeling Tours, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 39)
      498F.38
    - A Small Room, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 40)
      498F.39
    - Fairfax Wants Geological Survey, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 41)
      498F.40
    - Reston Names Rice Vice President, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 42)
      498F.41
    - Mix Colors with Care, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 43)
      498F.42
    - Planners Are Swinging Around to Golf Courses, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 44)
      498F.43
    - Agriculture Agency to Arrive, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 45)
      498F.44
    - Reston Fights Maryland Bid for US Agencies Plans 75,000 City by 1980, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 46)
      498F.45
    - Reston Developer Not At All Happy With State, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 47)
      498F.46
    - Virginia Called Derelict in Gaining US Offices, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 48)
      498F.47
    - Excerpts of Remarks by Secretary of the Interior Stewart L. Udall to the Harvard-Yale-Princeton Club, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 49)
      498F.48
    - Udall Changes 'Uglification' Of America, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 50)
      498F.49
    - ...And Air Conditioned Cities, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 51)
      498F.50
    - Reston Has Ideal Business Climate, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 52)
      498F.51
    - Today's Buyer Knows More Than Builder, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 53)
      498F.52
    - Planning Could Salvage Mile of Wisconsin Ave, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 54)
      498F.53
    - Columbia: City in the Country; Howard County, Maryland Will Be Locale of a Brand New City Designed to Create the Great Life for its People, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 55)
      498F.54
    - Town Plans Central Air Conditioning, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 56)
      498F.55
    - Financial Specialist Is Reston Vice President, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 57)
      498F.56
    - Udall Urges Challenge To Builders, Sees Reston As Wave of Future, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 58)
      498F.57
    - First Village Rising at Reston, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 59)
      498F.58
    - Code for Appraisers Outlined, Two Realtors Urge REliance on Land Use in Valuations, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 60)
      498F.59
    - Community Planner to Talk on Privacy, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 61)
      498F.60
    - Golf Lessons at Reston, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 62)
      498F.61
    - These May be the Right Kind of New Town, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 63)
      498F.62
    - The Appraiser, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 64)
      498F.63
    - Outdoor Recreation Group Seeks Plain of Action for Open Spaces, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 65)
      498F.64
    - This is the State of the Union: Free, Restless, Growing and Full of Hope, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 66)
      498F.65
    - Rail Transit, Highways Backed for Northern Virginia, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 67)
      498F.66
    - New-Community Growth Set at 500,000 by 1980, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 68)
      498F.67
    - The New Towns in Virginia Hunt County, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 69)
      498F.68
    - Where Will Foxes Go? Towns Challenge Suburban Sprawl, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 70)
      498F.69
    - Udall Sees Renaissance of US Cities, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 71)
      498F.70
    - High Rise Goes Up At Reston, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 72)
      498F.71
    - Individual Rated No. 1 at Reston, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 73)
      498F.72
    - Engineering in New Towns to be Seminar Subject, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 74)
      498F.73
    - Northern Virginia Continues Big Stride, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 75)
      498F.74
    - Publicity on Reston, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 76)
      498F.75
    - Letter from Mr. Goyert Jr. to Mr. Simon about a Copy of His Thesis He Gave to Simon, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 77)
      498G.01
    - Reston, Virginia, An Architectural History (Thesis Cover Page), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 78)
      498G.02
    - Lake Anne with Boats Tied to Docks and Apartment Buildings in Background (Photo), 1970s (Box 28, Folder 79)
      498G.03
    - Reston, Virginia Anne Architectural History Thesis Quote from Wolf Von Eckhardt, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 80)
      498G.04
    - Contour Map of Reston, Virginia, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 81)
      498G.05
    - Table of Contents, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 82)
      498G.06
    - Chapter One-Introduction to New Towns (p. 1-8), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 83)
      498G.07
    - The Reston Master Plan and Street Directory, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 84)
      498G.08
    - Chapter Two-Robert Simon (p. 9-12), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 85)
      498G.09
    - Chapter Three Economics (p. 13-16), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 86)
      498G.10
    - Ariel View of Reston Virginia (Drawing), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 87)
      498G.11
    - Chapter Four-Reston Planning Committee Zoning (p. 17-20), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 88)
      498G.12
    - Chapter Five-Economic Difficulty (p. 21-27), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 89)
      498G.13
    - Chapter Six-Change in Management (p. 28-34), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 90)
      498G.14
    - Chapter Seven-The Planning of Reston (p. 35-42), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 91)
      498G.15
    - Chapter Eight-The first Projects (p. 43-57), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 92)
      498G.16
    - Lake Anne and Homes (Photo), 1970s (Box 28, Folder 93)
      498G.17
    - Lake Anne Town Center (Photo), 1970s (Box 28, Folder 94)
      498G.18
    - Chapter Nine-Influences on the Planning (p. 58-64), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 95)
      498G.19
    - Lake Anne Plaza with Lake Anne in Background (Photo), 1970s (Box 28, Folder 96)
      498G.20
    - Golf Course Island, Reston, Virginia, 1970s (Box 28, Folder 97)
      498G.21
    - Chapter Ten-Later Projects and Gulf-Reston Incorporated Planning (p. 65-71), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      498G.22
    - Conclusion (p. 72-76), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      498G.23
    - Bibliography (p. 77-79), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      498G.24
    - Graphic Credits (p. 80), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      498G.25
    - Appendix A (p. 81-84), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      498G.26
    - Appendix B: Townhouses (p. 85-87), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      498G.27
    - Appendix C: Rental Projects (p. 88-89), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      498G.28
    - Appendix D: Subsidized Housing (p. 90-91), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      498G.29
    - Appendix E: Industrial and commercial Development (p.92), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      498G.30
    - Photograph of Foundation, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      499A.01
    - Photograph of Reston Land, Foundations and Lake, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      499A.02
    - Photograph of Houses, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 12)
      499A.03
    - Photograph of Buildings, Houses and Land, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 13)
      499A.04
    - Photograph of Buildings Being Built, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 14)
      499A.05
    - Photograph of Buildings, Houses and Apartments, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 15)
      499A.06
    - Photograph of Construction of Many Different Houses, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 16)
      499A.07
    - Photograph of a Newly Built "School" Building, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 17)
      499A.08
    - Reston: A Case for Cluster, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 18)
      499A.09
    - Photograph of Newly Built Apartment, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 19)
      499A.10
    - Photograph of Finished Apartments and Courtyard, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      499A.11
    - Photograph of Apartment and Driveway and Construction of Homes, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 21)
      499A.12
    - Photograph of Construction and Finished House and High Rise Building, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 22)
      499A.13
    - Photograph of Single Family Homes on the Waterfront, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 23)
      499A.14
    - Photograph of Pasterland With a Few Houses, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 24)
      499A.15
    - Photograph of Sculpture, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 25)
      499A.16
    - Photograph of Skeletal Buildings, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 26)
      499A.17
    - Photograph of Backside of Skeletal Buildings, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 27)
      499A.18
    - Photograph of Sculpture and Buildings/Construction, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 28)
      499A.19
    - Photograph of Lake Ann and Homes, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 29)
      499A.20
    - Photograph of Backside of Multi-family Dwelling, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 30)
      499A.21
    - Photograph of Frontside of Multi-family Dwellings, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 31)
      499A.22
    - Photograph of Multi-Family Dwellings Finished with Cars, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 32)
      499A.23
    - A Billion Dollar Bet on a New Way to Live, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 33)
      499A.24
    - Town-House Residents Enjoy 1,600 Acre Country Life Pleasures, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 34)
      499A.25
    - Reston's Urban Town Center Satisfies the Urban Urge, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 35)
      499A.26
    - Article With Different Pictures of Reston Life, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 36)
      499A.27
    - Town is Called 'A Brave Design', 1965 (Box 29, Folder 37)
      499A.28
    - Fully Planned Town Opens in Virginia, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 38)
      499A.29
    - Invitation to Lake Anne Village Center, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 39)
      499A.30
    - Part II of Invitation, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 40)
      499A.31
    - Growing Number of Arts Groups Reflect Pace of Cultural 'Boom', 1960s (Box 29, Folder 41)
      499A.36
    - She Returns Urbanity to Cities, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 42)
      499A.37
    - Her Housing Is Human, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 43)
      499A.38
    - Camera Advertisement, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 44)
      499A.39
    - Tomorrow's Towns, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 45)
      499A.32
    - Total Planning: Site of Town Near Washington, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 46)
      499A.33
    - Modern Living: New Towns, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 47)
      499A.34
    - 1,000 Meet Today in War on Blight, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 48)
      499A.35
    - The Case for Building 350 New Towns (p.1), 1960s (Box 29, Folder 49)
      499A.40
    - The Case for Building 350 New Towns (p.2), 1960s (Box 29, Folder 50)
      499A.41
    - The Case for Building 350 New Towns (p.3), 1960s (Box 29, Folder 51)
      499A.42
    - The Case for Building 350 New Towns (p.4), 1960s (Box 29, Folder 52)
      499A.43
    - Suppose You Could Drive Out Here This Weekend, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 53)
      499A.44
    - Map of Reston, Virginia, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 54)
      499A.45
    - Reston A Rural Ring, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 55)
      499A.46
    - Reston First of the New 'Satellite' Cities, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 56)
      499A.47
    - Publicity on Reston, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 57)
      499B.01
    - Washington Post-Laver Loses Reston Final to Rosewell, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 58)
      499B.02
    - The Sunday Star, Washington D.C.-Tennis Talk: Ornstein Girls in Orbit, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 59)
      499B.03
    - The Sunday Bulletin, Philadelphia Pennsylvania-Community Air Cooled by Central Plant, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 60)
      499B.04
    - Washington Daily News-Laver Opens at Reston, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 61)
      499B.05
    - Sunday Star-Rosewell and Laver Gain Reston Final, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 62)
      499B.06
    - Course Development Swings Right Along, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 63)
      499B.07
    - Washington Post-Semifinals today at Reston: Laver, Gonzalaz, Rosweall Wins, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 64)
      499B.08
    - 'This Is Private Property Isn't It?'-The Washington Daily News, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 65)
      499B.09
    - New town From the Ground Up-The Plain Dealer, Cleveland Ohio, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 66)
      499B.10
    - Gimeno Hopes Return to Area Means Success-The Evening Star, Washington D.C., 1965 (Box 29, Folder 67)
      499B.11
    - Everybody Walks in 'City of the Future'-Chicago Tribune, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 68)
      499B.12
    - The Virginian-Pilot, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 69)
      499B.13
    - The Evening Star, Washington D.C.-Stanley Rumbough Honored, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 70)
      499B.14
    - Washington Post-Reston Hiring 22 Students This Summer, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 71)
      499B.15
    - Washington Daily News-Gonzales Opens Play in Reston Pro-Tennis, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 72)
      499B.16
    - The Evening STar, Washington D.C.-Net Clinic Set by Pro Stars, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 73)
      499B.17
    - The Evening Star, Washington D.C.-Reston Hires Students for Summer Job, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 74)
      499B.18
    - New York Herald Tribune-Village Cooling System STarted, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 75)
      499B.19
    - La Stampa-Neglis Stati Uniti Impresari Privati Stanno Costruendo 75 Citta Giardino, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 76)
      499B.20
    - Florida AAA Motorist-"New Towns" and Child Safety Causing Stir in Real Estate, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 77)
      499B.21
    - The Sunday Star, Washington D.C.-Tennis Talk: Pros 'Arrival Makes Reston Grow', 1965 (Box 29, Folder 78)
      499B.22
    - The Washington Post-Pros Open pLay Today: Laver Seeded No. 1 at Reston, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 79)
      499B.23